PATRICIA CARR

PERSONAL WEBSITE: https://pcarrhi.github.io

BRIEF

My experience in managing all the Communications of a growing company allowed me to understand the importance of KPIs and its influence on decision making.

I transitioned into the Web Development field to challenge myself on learning new languages and gain new technical skills. An enriching experience at Altran helped me understand the importance of team organisation for the project's success.

I hope to utilise my technical & leadership skills to aid companies and their teams produce favorable outcomes to advance in their respective professional projects.

EDUCATION

Coding Academy by EPITECH

(European Institute of Technology)

Certificate of Completion Oct 2019-August 2020

University of Hawaii at Manoa

BA Communications & French, 2013 Cum Laude Honors

DETAILS

- +33 (0)6 51 82 03 56
- ▼ Toulouse, France
- pcarr.hi@gmail.com

SKILLS

Marketing/Tools:

- Google Analytics
- Copywriting
- PR / Presentations
- MS Office
- Agile Framework
 (JIRA and Confluence)

Programming experience:

- C
- HTML5/CSS3
- PHP
- Styled Components
- Angular 8/9
- Firebase
- React
- Python
- Mongo, Express, Node, React

WORK EXPERIENCE

ALTRAN

Web Developer Intern

MARCH 2020- JULY 2020 - TOULOUSE, FRANCE

- Work with project managers and other developers to understand each feature and time of completion to build components
- Review and utilize existing codebase to correct Front-End bug problems using Angular 8 or React
- Communicate with teammates on daily basis regarding code or technical issues

UWINLOC

Communications Manager (Geolocation Services)

JUN 2016- MAY 2019 - TOULOUSE, FRANCE

- Generate leads via videos, blogs, posters, website content.
- Maintain Press relations with journalists & Press Releases
- Internal Communication
- Manage social media content as well as KPI tracking
- Website Management through Wordpress
- Conduct Business Presentations/Pitching for new partnerships in France and within EU, USA, Japan, China
- Organize event logistics to maximize visibility at trade shows

Alliance Foundation Trials

Project Coordinator (Cancer Research)

JULY 2014 - OCT 2015 - BOSTON, USA

- Document management for clinical online portal
- Event Logistics Support Biannual Pharma trade show
- Meeting Minutes for Executive Board
- Feasibility study tracking for CRMs